

CONTACT

- **Website**
- tr.hakan.dagli@gmail.com
- **** (+90)5075420324
- Ankara
- in /hakandaglinet
- /hakandagli
- M <u>/@tr.hakan.dagli</u>

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering (3,14)

Süleyman Demirel University 2017-2021

Numerical Sciences (80,8)

M. Hakan Güvençer Science High School 2013-2017

OTHER INFOS

Country: Turkey

Date of birth: 29/01/1999 Place of birth: Ankara

Military: Completed (12/2023)

Driving License: B Merital Status: Single

LANGUAGES

English German
Reading B2 Reading A2
Speaking B2 Speaking A1
Writing B2 Writing A1

ABOUT

An experienced Software Engineer with a proven track record in defense industry projects, government initiatives, and e-commerce projects with daily tens of thousands of visitors.

He has been using Angular on the front-end for 3 years. Additionally, he has 16 months of experience with .NET on the back-end.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

MİA Teknoloji - Turkey 05.2024 - Current

Front-End Developer (Remote)

NTT DATA Business Solitions - Japan 01.2023 - 04.2024

Full Stack Developer

ARKSOFT Bilişim - Turkey 10.2021 - 01.2023

Front-End Developer

Akıllı Sınav - Turkey 04.2021-09.2021

SKILLS

Front-End

- ANGULAR
- Spartacus (SAP)
- HTML 5
- CSS 3 / SCSS / SASS
- JavaScript (ES6,ES7)
- TypeScript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- PrimeNG

Back-End

.NET CORE

REFERANCES

Mehmet SERT

NTT DATA / FE Team Lead lt.mehmetsert@gmail.com +90 554 995 55 42

Hüsamettin ELALMIŞ

Arksoft Bilişim/Team Lead helalmis@yahoo.com +90 535 560 34 90

Onur SAYGILI (in Germany)

Akıllı Sınav / CTO - Team Lead onursaygili@gmail.com

BLOGS

Javascript asenkron programala ve Event Loop kavramı (Coming Soon)

RxJS - Transformation
Operators

SAP Commerce Cloud-Spartacus -Angular Ortam Yapılandırması-SSR

<u>Javascript — var-let-const</u> <u>farkları ve scope kavramı</u>

HTML 5'e Giriş

HOBIES

- Football watching/playing
- Off-Road
- Camping
- Reading Literature
- Watching Movies, Series, Documentaries
- Phone and Computer Repairing
- Body Building

PROJECTS

NTT DATA Projects

<u>GRATIS.COM (Front-End)</u>
<u>SpeedyBunny(Front-End)</u> (Kuwait)
<u>TEKNOSA.COM (Front-End)</u>

ARKSOFT Projects

ARKLICENSE (Full Stack)

EDM (Front-End)

Easy2patch (Front-End)

SESSION AUDIT (Full Stack)

MIP (Front-End)

ARKSSPR (Front-End)

Akıllı Sınav Project

Akıllı Sınav Eğitim Modulü (Front-End)

INDIVIDUAL PROJECTS

arksoft.com.tr esinavmerkezi.com yurtoglukalip.com arksspr.com

GITHUB PROJECTS

Video Game Information Site

My Old Personal Website

Arrow Animation App

Okey Taşları

Bidirectional Linked List Animation App

Todo List Drag and Drop (Angular)

Todo List (Js)